Welcome to our first practical video on QA. Over the next couple of videos, we're going to focus on setup.
欢迎来到我们的第一个质量保证实践视频。接下来的几个视频，我们将重点讲解环境搭建。
The first piece of setup is that we need an API key, and we're going to use the OpenAI API.
搭建的第一步是需要获取API密钥，我们将使用OpenAI的API。
Let me just Google "OpenAI API". This is an overview. We need to go to platform.openai.com.
让我先谷歌搜索"OpenAI API"。这是概述页面，我们需要访问platform.openai.com。
You need to log in. Creating an account is absolutely free, but you do need to log in to get an API key.
需要先登录。注册账户完全免费，但必须登录才能获取API密钥。
Let me log in for myself, and I'll show you how to generate an API key.
我先登录自己的账号，然后给大家演示如何生成API密钥。
It's possible that you might still have a free tier available.
你可能还有免费额度可以使用。
However, what we're going to do throughout this course won't cost you more than one US dollar.
不过整个课程的操作花费不会超过1美元。
With the caveat that the minimum credit you can add is five US dollars.
需要注意的是最低充值金额是5美元。
But seriously, it will cost less than one dollar. Now let me figure this out - I always get lost here.
但实际花费真的不到1美元。现在我来操作一下——我经常在这里迷路。
This platform keeps getting bigger and bigger. Okay, I would say go to the dashboard.
这个平台越来越庞大了。好的，我建议先进入控制面板。
Then select API keys, and to create one, click on "Create". Let me name it "AI agent".
然后选择API密钥，点击"创建"新建一个。我把它命名为"AI代理"。
I'll give it all permissions. It should be your account as well, so this should be okay.
我会授予全部权限。因为是你们自己的账户，这样设置没问题。
Now it's very important that you copy this key - this is the only time it will be shown.
现在非常关键的是要复制这个密钥——这是它唯一一次显示。
It appears just once, so you need to copy and store it securely somewhere.
它只出现一次，所以必须复制并安全保存。
For our purposes, if you haven't already, I'd encourage you to download the AI agents folder.
建议你们下载AI代理文件夹（如果还没下载的话）。
Then go to "Crew AI job interview prep part one", click on "New", then "More", and select Google Colaboratory.
然后进入"Crew AI面试准备第一部分"，点击"新建"，选择"更多"，再选Google Colaboratory。
From here we can begin. What I'll do now is click on "Copy".
从这里我们就可以开始了。我现在要点击"复制"。
And like I have already quite a bit, but let me add another secret here. You can see that I have been working on this.
就像我之前已经展示了不少内容，但让我再添加一个秘密。你们可以看到我一直在处理这个。
Let me call it "AI agents, OpenAI". Right. So this will be a key that I'm going to use specifically for this course.
我把它命名为"AI agents, OpenAI"。好的，这将是我专门为这个课程使用的密钥。
I do Ctrl+V to paste it here, and let me hide it here. Then the last piece that one would do is click here.
我按Ctrl+V粘贴到这里，然后把它隐藏起来。最后一步就是点击这里。
This is going to get here the code in order to get a specific API key. For instance, I would come here to "AI agents, OpenAI".
这里会生成获取特定API密钥的代码。比如说，我会找到这个"AI agents, OpenAI"。
I would store it under something. Let's say "OpenAI API key equals to this OpenAI API key".
我会把它存储为某个变量。比如说"OpenAI API key等于这个OpenAI API密钥"。
Let me just add here so we'll focus it on setup. The very basics of things would be okay.
让我在这里添加一下，这样我们就能专注于设置了。最基础的内容就足够了。
Ctrl+Enter and let me come here to secrets at the same time. Currently it's connecting to the script.
按Ctrl+Enter，同时让我来到secrets这里。现在它正在连接到脚本。
You see here "notebook access". What is happening is that all of these secrets are passed from one notebook to the other.
你们看到这里的"notebook access"。实际上所有这些密钥都会从一个笔记本传递到另一个笔记本。
But you do need to activate for that specific notebook. In this case, it's going to prompt you "grant access".
但你需要为特定笔记本激活。在这里，它会提示你"grant access"。
You come to grant access, and then I can see I took way too long. It's okay.
你点击授权访问，然后我发现我花了太长时间。没关系。
I do Ctrl+Enter and here we go. Now we have the OpenAI API key, which is absolutely ready to go.
我按下Ctrl+Enter，好了。现在我们有了OpenAI API密钥，已经完全准备就绪了。
With this, I'm going to stop this video. Let me just give it a title here: "CrewAI job interview prep part one".
到这里，我要结束这个视频了。让我给它加个标题："CrewAI工作面试准备第一部分"。
Here we go. And that is it. I'll see you in the next video.
好了，就这样。我们下个视频见。